你見到呢個tray？
我係自己整嘅
You're an
unfamiliar face
Get yourself a
permit if you're looking to do business here
Last thing I need
is an unlicensed hooker
Can't make as
much cash when you're legal
Yeah
good luck
with that
I just need
permission from him
don't I？
Let me meet him
Sorry
I got no idea
who you mean
I'll keep coming
back until I meet him
Until I
meet the baby
You can't catch
the ball with your hands like that
You're not
the goalkeeper
Quit your whining
who died and
made you repp？
Where the hell
did Dugout go？
Where'd Hugo？
Tenma，dummy，Tenma
He told me to
stay with you for a while
Cause he found
the man he was looking for
That's all
Who leaves a kid
with someone like me？
No way in hell
Thanks a lot，Tema
I have to babysit
I hate kids
First he drops
off the face of the earth
And then he
saddles me with some random brat
Me and him
had an agreement
Doesn't that mean
nothing anymore？
What the hell kind of doctor doesn't want to make some easy money？
Here
Hey，nice header
Son of a…
Did I look like I
was ready to you？
Hey
remember
what I said
you can't
use your hands
That's a
yellow card
I'm throwing
this into traffic
If you mention
the rules one more time
You keep
talking like that
you'll get
a red card
Shut up
Why the hell
are you so late？
Hurry up and
give me the stuff
Give me
the stuff now
Long time no see
Detective Messner
Doctor Tanma？
But…
That's right
That's exactly
what you called me back when we first met
Before I even got
around to telling you what my occupation was
But that was a
long time ago
My days in
medicine are over
But I suppose you'
re no longer a detective
Detective suspended on narcotics charges
This article really came as a shock when I read it six months ago
Don't even think
about running away
I have a gun
trained on you under my jacket
Alright，what do
you want with me？
I need answers
what happened in
Heidelberg almost a year ago
And who was
behind it all？
Who ordered you
to do such a terrible thing？
I…I don't
know anything
You killed the
Fordners and Mr， Mower from the post
It wasn't me
that did it
I was hired
as the lookout
that's all
My partner Mueller
he did it
he killed
all of them
Detective Mueller
also left the force soon after the murders
Yeah，he did
I hear that he'
s very well off
Turns out he's
doing good with his money
You，on the
other hand
ended up wasting
all of your money on your drug habit
That sound
about right？
He was the one
who took on the job
And he was the
one who committed the murders
He ended up getting the largest portion of the reward
They even tried
to get rid of me
They tried to kill me to make sure I didn't go to the cops
I'm surprised you'
re still breathing
It was the
organisation that helped me
Organisation？
Enough
I already told
her too much as it is
Told her？
Her who？
Leave me alone
already，I can't…
I can't deal
with you right now
Looks like you're
going through withdrawal
And with me
sitting here
no dealer would
come within 20 feet of you
So I suggest
you start talking
I…
I was…
I was saved
by the baby
The baby？
Go to a pub
called Candy
you can find
him there，Wait
who's this baby
you're talking about？
He's a right
wing extremist
He's also a high
official in two of their major political parties
After the
wall fell
The baby tried to
create a town of only pureblooded Germans
But his plan
failed and now he's come back
But why'd
he do it？
Why'd he
bother saving you？
The darkness
After the
Berlin Wall fell
A great
darkness was created
A monster…
A monster was born
A monster？
Now leave me alone
I've already said
everything to that girl
You understand？
What girl
Messner？
She came for
revenge and pointed a gun at me
She's the daughter of that older couple we murdered
You're
saying Anna？
I mean Nina
Nina Fortner
came to see you then？
The…
the baby said
to me that I…
that I was to
send that girl to him if I ever saw her
or if she ever
showed up around these parts
He said that…
that she's
important to use as bait
He's using her…
as bait？
You don't give up
do ya？
You're getting to
be a regular coming back all the time
How about I rent
you for an hour or two
so the night ain'
t a total waste？
You're the one
who said I'd get in trouble
if I did business
without the baby's permission
Well，we got
ourselves a mouthy one
Yeah，not so
clever now
are ya？
Is this the girl
who keeps asking to see the baby？
Yes sir
It seems you're
getting your wish
Don't keep
him waiting
Please wait
right here
Miss
Stand on
that eye motif
if you'd
be so kind
Directly
over the iris
please
Yes，much better
Now tell me
Nina Fortner
Doesn't this song resonate with you right down to the soles of your feet？
I have to dance
The baby told me
The day another
Hitler is born to us
Our country
will be saved
The girl will be
the perfect
bait for him
Nina
How is it that
you know my name？
That's the
least of what I know
You've also answered to the name of Anna Liebert
But the former is
just as false as the latter
A rose by any
other name does smell as sweet
But they
call me the baby
so I'm biased
Come on
let's cut the rug a bit
Is it true that
you know where my brother is right now？
Yohan，right？
Good name，yes
You know
don't you？
What are you going to do when you finally have your little family reunion？
I'm going to
take him down
You shouldn't
whip that out willy nilly
Miss，Someone's
liable to get hurt
Patience，dear，Why
I'm sure Johann
is searching for you even as we speak
I lived around
here when I was your age
Know this place
like the back of my hand
There's a fellow
who buys antiques
And I sell him
this rug I stumbled across
What do you mean？ Don't you have any money left， Mr Heckle？ Shut your yap already
I'm hawking this
rug so I can get the two of us something to eat
I don't hear you
coming up with…
Son of a…
There goes the
neighbourhood
Mr Heckle
what's wrong？
Turks
This whole area
is full of turks now
Hmm
your socalled
heirloom is a fake
Huh？What are
you talking about？
Feel it
handwoven silk
You can't fake
this kind of quality
It's synthetic
Tell you what
I'll give you a
hundred marks for it out of sheer sympathy
More like
sheer chicanery
The German guy who had this place would have given me ten grand
Well，you can
take it or leave it
Don't you come crying to me when you realise my rug is the real deal
That one hanging
on the wall is the real deal
It's a
genuine Hetikay rug
There's your
handwoven silk
Look at the
detail there in the patterns
It's perfect
150，000 marks
You sure got
took for a ride
If you really can'
t tell the good stuff from that crap
I feel
sorry for you
We're outta here
Dieder
Hey
I'm getting
kinda hungry
That rug's real
It's a henna cake
just like he said
Only a hundred
and fifty grand？
I could get eight
hundred thousand for a rug as fancy as that
Come on
let's get
something to eat already
Shut up
If I can get my
hands on that rug
We'll be able to
eat anything we want
How you
gonna do that？
What are you
talking about？
I'm sure I'll
think of something
huh？
Don't
gimme that look
You're hungry
aint you？
Whatever，thief
What？
Put a sock in
it ya little brat
Geez
Hold on a second
Where do you
think you're going？
Sorry
but I'm not
looking to buy
That's not
what I meant
Are you crazy？
An Asian like you is gonna get killed if you walk into a place like that
They don't take
kindly to foreigners in there
But you're Turkish
aren't you？
Is it alright for
you to be doing business around here？
What are
you stupid？
I wouldn't do
business in a dump like this
A friend of mine was just abducted by a bunch of guys who are regulars there
What？
It seems like she
found out a secret of theirs
A secret？
I don't know
what it's all about
But I have to
find her before something bad happens
Who knows what
they're going to do to her？
A woman I know
is in there too
I have to
get her out
Who is she？
What does this
woman look like？
Does she have
long blonde hair？
Don't know
I couldn't tell
you what she looks like now
Because they just
took a young blonde girl away in a car
Where'd
they take her？
Hey，how
should I know？
But the baby
was with them
so they probably
went to his mansion
The baby？
What kind of car？
What
colour was it？
It was big and red
I don't know
Alright then
I've gotta track
down that red car before it's too late
Wait
you have to do
something to help my friend too
Please help her
she has a
small baby
If something
happens to her…
Please
You're
still alive？
This is my
lucky day
This way please
Without your gun
on this point
I'm afraid I
must insist
Thank you for
your cooperation
Go ahead and sit
wherever you like
So the baby
brought you in， eh？
Eyes forward
let me see your face
Goodness
But I should have
known you'd be quite a beauty
After all
you are Johann'
s twin sister
My name is
Professor Giedlitz
And the man standing next to Johann in the picture is General Wolff
We created
this organisation
along with a pair
of other likeminded individuals
Where are
my manners？
Would you care
for some fruit？
No，thank you
I want to
see Johann
And see
him you will
Once he knows
that you're here
no force on earth
could keep him away
The boy suffers
mightily in your absence
You people don't
know where Johann is either
do you？
We need him
His country needs him
We four shall
help him fulfil his destiny
Do you have any
idea how Hitler became possessed of such power？
It's because he
saw the three things a person would have to do
to gain
control of a country
Manipulate
the banks
feed the
war machine
and take command
of the military
I'm sure Johann's
working on one of those things right now
Or two
really it's a
question of if
not when
What exactly do
you plan to do with Johann？
Think of it
Hitler bent a weakened nation to his will using nothing but raw charisma
All that from a
man who only made corporal
A man whom art
school wouldn't deign to let in
His charisma
appeared after he hit his 30s
Not so with
your brother Johan
He was a leader
of men even as a mere boy
Charisma of
messianic proportions
But even Jesus
Christ had help
Consider the
three Magi and John the Baptist
Who heralded the
Saviour's arrival into the world
How they readied
the way for His glory
Likewise
the four of us
have been keeping track of Johann's talents
Ever since he
was a little boy
Exciting
wouldn't you say？
What is it that
you want with me？
Please accept
our hospitality
Until Johann comes looking for you at the very least
Actually
I'm afraid I
must insist
You know too much
for us to let you walk away now
Don't worry
about that
I came here of
my own volition
I will wait
here for Johann
Then we agree
Now then
you should at
least try the fruit
Good，you're
finally awake
Don't look
so worried
we're not
going to hurt you
Not right
away at least
So what brings
you to my little slice of the world？
Dr， Tenma，Wait
how do you
already know what my name is？
Why don't you
leave the questions to me？
Now all you have
to do is answer
Why exactly were
you snooping around？
I know you're
looking for Johann
but I can't
figure out why
Where are you
keeping Nina？
I told you to
leave the questions to me
did I not？
What are you
gonna do with her？
Why do you
insist on vexing me？
Nina is our guest
whereas you are just a meddlesome piece of trash to be disposed of
So
is she okay？
At the moment
but that'll
change soon enough
She's determined to kill Johann
and we simply
can't have that
Always a shame
when a pretty girl dies before her time
You're just using
Nina as bait to draw out Johann？
What are you
planning on doing？
Who the
hell are you？
That is enough
A person of impure race has no right to ask those questions
Their souls just
never know their place
Which is why we'
re putting the Turkish quarter to the torch
The whole quarter？
Indeed
The night sky
tomorrow will be a thing of beauty
A fiery cleansing
If I stay here
then I'll
find Johann
Please help
help me
Who…
who are you？
Please
I beg of you
Okay
where are
you right now？
The third floor
It sounds like you
're speaking with an accent
Where are
you from？
I'm Turkish
Please
I've got to escape
They're
going to kill me
Have you been
taken prisoner by the people here？
Help me
please
I can't
They're
watching me closely
I've got to
stay in here
Please
help me escape
I have to
warn the others
or my baby
will die too
Tomorrow night
we celebrate in
honour of Johann's homecoming
Only the members
of the pure master race like us deserve to survive
Everything else
should just burn away
I overheard
them talking
They're going to
burn it all down tomorrow night
They're
going to destroy
The Turkish
part of town
Help me
please help me